Subtitle By : GoldenBeard Improved By : Fidel33 Sub Upload Date : June 29 , 2018
( WIND BLOWING )
( SIGHS SOFTLY )
He 's okay .
Rocket .
Very good job !
That 's how ...
That 's how ... we 'll get away .
( GASPING )
Go find your mother .
For the radio ?
Might help us boost the signal .
For you .
Thank you .
It 'll be dark soon .
Listen to me ...
Too loud .
( BIRDS CAWING )
( TOY BEEPING )
( TOY WHIRRING )
( BEEPING CONTINUES )
( BRANCHES SNAPPING )
( WIND BLOWING )
( RADIO STATIC CRACKLING )
S.
( SIZZLING )
( EXHALES )
Dinner .
REGAN : (
WHISPERING ) One , two , three , four , five , six , seven , eight .
( GLASS SHATTERING )
( BIRDS SCREECHING AND FLYING AWAY )
( LOUD CRASHING )
( METAL CREAKING )
( METAL GROANING )
( SHRIEKING )
( EXHALES )
(
MOUTHING ) I 'm sorry .
( RACCOONS CHITTERING )
( SQUEALS )
( FEEDBACK WHINING )
Beautiful .
I didn 't say anything .
( MUSIC PLAYING THROUGH HEADPHONES )
♪ Come a little bit closer ♪
♪ Hear what I have to say ♪
♪ Just like children sleeping ♪
♪ We could dream this night away ♪
♪ But there 's a full moon rising ♪
♪ Let 's go dancing in the light ♪
♪ We know where the music 's playing ♪
♪ Let 's go out and feel the night ♪
( PUMPING )
( FETAL HEART BEATING )
You cannot go down there !
Why not ?
You know why .
I 'm not a child ! I won 't make a sound !
Just don 't .
Please .
This time , I took small amplifiers from the stereo .
It .
It . Won 't .
It . Won 't . Work .
No , this should increase the frequency to ...
It .
It . Never .
It . Never . Works !
But ...
we 'll keep trying
until it does .
( LEE SIGHS )
Stop .
Just
( SOBS )
Remember , you need to divide .
Carry the three .
Amazing !
( FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING )
Time to go .
... please don 't make me go ...
You 'll be fine .
Your father will always protect you .
Your father will always protect you . Always .
Listen to me ...
It 's important that you learn these things .
He just wants you to be able to take care of yourself .
... to take care of me .
... when I 'm old
and grey
and I have no teeth ...
(
WHISPERING ) Don 't worry .
I don 't want to go .
There 's nothing to be scared of .
... of course there is .
I 'll go .
I need you to stay and help your mother .
I want to go .
Just stay here .
You 'll be safe .
... next time .
( MUFFLED THUD )
( LIGHT FEEDBACK WHINING )
( INAUDIBLE )
( WHISPERING )
They 'll hear you .
Look at me .
Listen .
The river ...
The river ... is loud .
Small sounds ...
Small sounds ... safe .
Big sounds ...
Big sounds ... not safe .
Unless ...
there 's another sound nearby ...
there 's another sound nearby ... that 's louder .
You 're safe .
I wanna show you something .
( GASPS )
( EXHALES )
( WATERFALL ROARING )
( HOOTS LOUDLY )
( ALOUD ) Hey ,
you 're all right .
You 're all right .
I promise .
( MUFFLED HOOT )
( ALOUD ) Why didn 't you let her come ?
Do you blame her ...
for what happened ?
No .
Because she blames herself .
( SNIFFLES )
It was no one 's fault .
You still love her , right ?
Of course I do .
( NO SOUNDS )
You should tell her .
( FAINT CREAKING )
( FLIES BUZZING )
( SCREAMS )
( RUSTLING )
( CLACKING )
( SNARLING AND GROWLING )
( CREATURE SCREECHING )
( WHIMPERING SOFTLY )
( INHALES DEEPLY )
( GROANS )
( GLASS SHATTERING )
( SOBBING QUIETLY )
( SHUDDERS )
( CREATURE SCREECHING )
( CLACKING )
( CRASHING )
( STIFLED MOAN )
( EXHALING )
( CLACKING )
( GROWLING AND CLACKING )
( CREAKING )
( SNARLS )
( HISSING AND CLACKING )
( GROWLING )
( CLACKING )
( STIFLED SOB )
( TIMER TICKING )
( TIMER BELL RINGING )
( GROWLING AND SNARLING )
( CREATURE SHRIEKING )
( CLACKING )
Rocket .
I need you ...
I need you ... to make a sound ...
I need you ... to make a sound ... that 's louder .
Your mother ...
Your mother ... needs your help .
You .
You . Can .
You . Can . Do this .
( SIGHS )
( STIFLED MOAN )
( SHUDDERING )
- (
RUSTLING ) - ( GASPS )
( GROWLING )
( NEARBY RUSTLING )
( STIFLED MOANS )
( CLACKING )
( LOUD WHISTLING AND EXPLOSION )
( CREATURE ROARING )
( SCREAMING )
( EXPLOSIONS )
( WHISTLING AND EXPLOSIONS CONTINUING )
( INHALES )
( EXHALES )
( BABY COOING )
( PANTING )
( BRANCHES SNAPPING )
( CREATURE SCREECHING )
( GROWLING )
( BABY COOING )
( BABY FUSSES )
( BABY CRYING )
( WAILING LOUDLY )
( BABY CONTINUES FUSSING )
- ( MUFFLED ROARS
OVERHEAD ) - LEE : Shh ...
( BABY CONTINUES FUSSING )
( OXYGEN TANK HISSING )
( GROWLING OVERHEAD )
( MUFFLED FUSSING )
( LOUD ROARING )
( CRYING MUFFLED )
( CREATURE SNARLING QUIETLY )
( FEEDBACK WHINING )
( WHINING CONTINUES )
( CREATURE SNARLING )
( CREATURE SCREECHES )
( WHINING STOPS )
- ( GASPS ) - LEE : Shh ...
( ALOUD ) It 's okay . It 's okay .
You 're safe .
They can 't hear us .
It worked .
You just need to rest now .
Where are they ?
I 'll find them .
No , she was with me . She was with me , and ...
then I had to go and do laundry , and ...
He was with you . How did he ...
Rockets .
So he 'd still be there .
- I 'm sure he is . - He knows to wait for you .
And she is ...
She 's smart . She 'll have found a place .
They know what to do .
( BABY COOING )
It 's a boy .
I could 've carried him .
He was so heavy , wasn 't he ?
I can still ...
I can still feel the weight in my arms .
Small , but
so heavy .
( SOFTLY ) And my hands were free .
I was carrying the bag , but my hands were free .
You have to stop .
So , I could 've carried him .
I should 've carried him .
Who are we
if we can 't protect them ?
Who are we ?
You have to protect them .
Promise me
you will protect them .
( WATER TRICKLING )
( WATER RUNNING )
Don 't worry ...
Don 't worry ... he 'll come for us .
( WATER RUNNING )
( SNARLING SOFTLY )
( BABY COOING )
( BABY GURGLES )
( CREATURE HISSING )
( GROWLING )
We can 't stay here .
We need to go .
He 'll come for us .
He will come for us .
He 'll come for you !
No , you 're wrong .
He told me !
Don 't move .
Stop .
( CLANGING )
( PANTING )
( GASPING )
( GASPS )
( METAL CREAKING )
( GROWLING )
( ROARING )
( FEEDBACK WHINING )
( ROARING ANGRILY )
( FEEDBACK WHINING CONTINUES )
( PAINED SCREECHING AND SNARLING )
( CREATURE SHRIEKING )
( SNARLING )
( PANTING )
Are you okay ?
You okay ?
( DISTANT SNARLING )
( RUSTLING )
Let 's get to the truck .
( SNARLING )
- ( SCREAMS ) Dad ! - ( GASPS )
( GROWLING )
( FEEDBACK WHINING )
( WHINING CONTINUES )
( WHINING STOPS )
( SNARLING )
( AXE THUDS )
I
I love
I love you .
I
I have
I have always
I have always loved
I have always loved you .
( SCREAMING )
( SNARLING )
( SCREECHING )
( SOBBING QUIETLY )
( ROARING IN DISTANCE )
( CLACKING )
( RUMBLING IN DISTANCE )
( BABY COOING SOFTLY )
( THUDDING )
( THUDDING CONTINUES )
( SNARLING )
( HISSING )
( CLACKING )
( TELEVISION STATIC )
( TELEVISION STATIC CONTINUES )
( SHRIEKS )
( GASPS )
( LOW SNARLING )
( FEEDBACK WHINING )
( FEEDBACK WHINING CONTINUES )
( CREATURE SQUEALING )
( WAILING LOUDLY )
( FEEDBACK AMPLIFIED )
( SCREECHING )
( FEEDBACK STOPS )
( ROARING AND SNARLING )
( FAINT RUMBLING )
( COOING )
Improved By : Fidel33 Sub Upload Date : June 29 , 2018